

# **NODIRBEK ULASHEV**

## JavaScript Engineer

Full-stack Web Developer

#### **SUMMARY**

As a JavaScript developer with background in developing and managing web applications, I am passionate about staying up to date with the latest technologies and continuing to grow in my career. With my skills and experience, I am confident in my abilities to deliver software solutions that meet the needs of businesses and end-users alike.

#### **SKILLS**

- · HTML5 & CSS3
- · JavaScript (ES5 ESNext)
- · ReactJs & NextJs & Redux
- · Shopify App & Liquid Development
- TypeScript
- NestJs & ExpressJs
- · Webpack & Vite
- · MongoDB & Mongoose

#### **LANGUAGES**

ENGLISH C1, Advanced

RUSSIAN B2, Upper-Intermediate

**UZBEK** Native

## CONTACT

**3** +998 99 +998 99

nodirbekulashev01@gmail.com

Tashkent, Shaykhantakhur, 100020 Uzbekistan

#### **LINKS**

in

www.min1one.com

www.linkedin.com/in/n-ulashev-min1one

t.me/MiN10ne

github.com/MiN10ne

●● <u>medium.com/@nodirbekulashev01</u>

#### **EXPERIENCE**

JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER July 2021 - Current

LlamaCommerce, Remote, New York 10013 USA www.llamacommerce.io

- · Developing and maintaining Shopify based online stores.
- Developing Shopify applications (client-side & post-purchase & theme-appextensions).
- · Developing custom business logic using Storefont and Admin APIs.
- · Integrating third-party services.
- · Creating responsive UIs and modular components.
- · Creating project workflows, scripts and setting up CI/CD.
- · Analyzing and optimizing product performance, structure and architecture.
- · Estimating and setting right deadlines.
- Taking part in code reviews and providing feedback.
- · Proposing technical solutions based on viable documentations.
- · Assisting newcomer developers in getting started with company tech-stack.

## Contributed projects:

- · www.bugatchi.com
- · www.wildone.com
- www.b2b.kassatex.com
- · Upsell and Cross Sell apps.shopify.com/upsell-prod
- Manual Related Products apps.shopify.com/related-products-app

#### JAVASCRIPT INTERN July 2021 - Aug 2021

EPAM Systems, Remote, Tashkent Uzbekistan www.epam.com

- · Took part in teamwork.
- · Learnt basics of NestJs and practiced git commands and workflows.
- Was assigned to complete a demo project with required technologies that have to be learnt in the process of development.

## FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER Dec 2020 - June 2021

Self-employed, Tashkent Uzbekistan

- · Laying out front-end of online stores, landing pages and web applications
- · Developing MVPs.
- Understaning needs & proposing project plans and appropriate tech solutions.

#### Contributed projects:

• www.softit.uz

- <u>jobfront.inminternational.uz</u>
- www.uzbtrip.com
- 180Gradus

### **EDUCATION**

Aug 2019 - May 2023

#### **BACHELOR OF SCIENCE - MANAGEMENT INFORMATION SYSTEMS**

Webster University, Tashkent Uzbekistan, 3.27 GPA

Focus on Project Management, System Design, Basic Programming, Basic Financial and Managerial Accounting